* Search
* Navigation

Popular topics: [Community Guidelines](https://support.bitchute.com/policy/guidelines), [Cookie Policy](https://support.bitchute.com/policy/cookie)

Sorry, we didn't find any relevant articles for you.

Please fill out the contact form below and we will reply as soon as possible.

Your email 

Your question 

Description (details)

### Table of Contents

Privacy Policy
==============

**Latest Update: August 17, 2024**

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Deep State Protocol LLC ("DSP") collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from Users (each, a "User") of the BitChute website and associated services (collectively known as the "Service"). This privacy policy applies to all elements of the Service. Please ensure that you read this Privacy Policy, the [**Terms & Conditions**](https://support.bitchute.com/policy/terms) and the [**Cookie Policy**](https://support.bitchute.com/policy/cookie) carefully. These are collectively known as the "Terms".

#### Your acceptance of these Terms

By using the Service, you are agreeing to be bound by these Terms. If you do not agree with these Terms, then please do not use the Service. Your continued use of the Service following the posting of changes to these Terms will be deemed as your acceptance of those changes. If you are accessing and using the Service on behalf of a company (such as your employer) or another legal entity, then you represent and warrant that you have the authority to bind that company or other legal entity to these Terms. In that case, "you" and "your" will refer to that company or other legal entity.

#### Changes to the Terms and/or Service

DSP has the discretion to update the Terms at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the top of this page. It is important that you frequently review the Terms for any changes to stay informed. By using the Service, you acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review the Terms periodically to become aware of modifications. As our Service is constantly evolving over time, we may change or discontinue all or any part of the Service, at any time and without notice, at our sole discretion.

#### Terms & Conditions

Please refer to the [**Terms & Conditions**](https://support.bitchute.com/policy/terms) for more information on the expected use of the Service.

#### Cookie Policy

Please refer to the [**Cookie Policy**](https://support.bitchute.com/policy/cookie) for more information on cookies we utilize.

What information do we collect
------------------------------

We collect information from Users in a variety of ways, including but not limited to: when Users use Service, register for the Service, place an order, subscribe to a channel or discussion, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available. In some cases you share this information directly with us, e.g., by registering for an account; we also collect information automatically from you through technology (e.g., your device or browser type, your activity on the Service).

#### Personal Identification Information

The collection of personal identification information is limited to Registered Users of the Service. Registered Users may be asked for, as appropriate for the goods and services they are utilising: their first and last name, age, residential address, delivery address, billing address, email address, phone number, and/or payment card details. Such personal identification information will only be collected from Registered Users if they voluntarily submit such information to us.

Data will be processed by DSP in a way that is crucial to evidencing assent to a contract, as well as to performing steps comprising that contract's fulfillment, including delivery of the wider Service.

Users can always refuse to supply personal identification information, with the understanding that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Service related activities. Users have the right to see the content of their data and to have corrections made to it.

Explicit consent to this Privacy Policy is required when registering as a User of the Service.

#### Non-personal Identification Information

We may collect non-personal identification information about all Users whenever they interact with the Service. This may include details of the type of device, the operating system, the browser, and information about the means of connection to the Service, such as Internet Service Providers utilized and other similar related information.

How we use the information
--------------------------

We may collect and use Users information for the following purposes:

1. To improve customer service. Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.
2. To improve the Service. We may use feedback you provide to perform site traffic analysis and improve our products and services.
3. To run a promotion, contest, survey or other feature. To send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them.
4. To send periodic emails. We may use the email address to send User information and updates pertaining to their subscriptions, activity and/or orders. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

How we protect the information
------------------------------

We adopt appropriate collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and associated data stored on our Service.

Sensitive and private exchanges between the Service and its Users happen over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures.

How we share the information
----------------------------

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users' personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above. We may occasionally share information collected with our professional advisors (including accountants, auditors, lawyers, and consultants) when reasonably necessary for them to perform services for us and give us appropriate advice. Finally, we may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Service or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your personal identification information with these third parties for those limited purposes, provided that you have given us your consent.

In special limited circumstances we may be required to disclose your data without express consent, these are:

1. When we have a good faith belief it is required by law.
2. When we have a good faith belief it is necessary to protect our or others' rights or property.
3. To any successor or purchaser in a merger, acquisition, liquidation, dissolution or sale of assets.

Your consent will not be required for disclosure in these cases, but we will attempt to notify you, to the extent permitted by law to do so.

Tracking Technologies and Advertising
-------------------------------------

Your browser settings may allow you to automatically transmit a "Do Not Track" signal to online services you visit. Note, however, there is not consensus among industry participants as to what "Do Not Track" means in this context. Like many online services, we currently do not alter our practices when we receive a "Do Not Track" signal from a visitor's browser. To find out more about "Do Not Track," [**click here**](https://allaboutdnt.com/), but note we do not take responsibility for the completeness or accuracy of this or any other information provided by third parties.

We use **Google Analytics** to perform site traffic analysis (not for advertising or marketing purposes). Google provides a browser extension you can use to opt-out of having your site activity available to Google Analytics. For more information [**see this support page from Google**](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/181881?hl=en)**.**

Many advertisers and service providers performing advertising-related services for us participate in voluntary programs which provide tools that users can use to opt-out of interest-based advertising. One such program is the Digital Advertising Alliance's Self-Regulatory Program for Online Behavioral Advertising. To learn more about this program and how you can express your preferences, [**click here**](https://youradchoices.com/control). Another such program is the Network Advertising Initiative, which you can learn about by [**clicking here**](https://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1).

Note that opting-out of interest-based advertising via the above programs (or similar) means only that those selected, voluntarily participating program members should no longer deliver such advertising to you, but it does not mean you will no longer receive any targeted content and/or ads. In addition, if your browsers are configured to reject cookies generally at the time when you visit the websites of these opt-out programs, or if you subsequently erase the cookies installed by them, or use a different device or web browser, your browser-based opt-out may no longer be effective.

We may use third-party services to help us deliver advertising messages to you. You may exercise your choices regarding the use of cookies by using options provided in the messages displayed to you on our site. Note that DSP offers the ability for Registered Users to opt out of advertising entirely with the effect that this code will not be running on the version of the Service delivered to them. Go under Settings > Interface and scroll down to uncheck the "Show Adverts" box to exercise this option. Note, however, that advertising helps us cover the cost of delivering the Service. So if you decide to exercise this option, please consider supporting the platform with a [**BitChute Membership**](https://www.bitchute.com/membership/) package.

How long we keep your information
---------------------------------

We keep the categories of personal information described above for as long as is necessary for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy or otherwise authorized by law. Generally, we will keep the data we collect when you use our products or services for a maximum of one year. However, note that we will continue to hold the information as long as any of the following is still applicable:

* Your personal information is reasonably necessary to manage our operations, to manage your relationship with us, or to satisfy another purpose for which we collected the information;
* The information is reasonably required to protect or defend our rights or property (which will generally relate to applicable laws that limit actions in a particular case); or
* We are otherwise permitted or required to keep your information by applicable laws or regulations.

Withdrawal of consent
---------------------

If at any time a Registered User wishes to withdraw their consent to this policy they can do so via their account settings page. Withdrawal of consent will result in the Account concerned being suspended and scheduled for termination. All content, activity and associated information relating to the Account will be removed as part of this process.

We also provide the following options which you may exercise, as follows:

* Opting Out of Promotional Communications: Opt out of commercial messages we send to you by clicking on the "unsubscribe" link provided with each message. Note that this does not apply to transactional communications, such as those related to your account registration, any required or important notices related to your use of our Service, or to the fulfillment of a specific transaction.
* Regardless of your jurisdiction of domicile, DSP honors requests to exercise Data Subject Access Rights (right of access to personal data/right to know, right to correction, right to erasure, right to withdraw consent, right to restriction of processing, right to data portability, right to object, and right to opt out of the sale of personal information). To exercise any of these rights, please contact us at [**privacy@bitchute.com**](mailto:privacy@bitchute.com) or DSP, Attn: BitChute Privacy, 30 N. Gould Street, Suite N, Sheridan, WY  82801. Please note, however, that the above rights are not absolute, and we may be entitled to refuse requests, wholly or partly, where exceptions under the applicable law apply.

Jurisdiction-specific terms
---------------------------

#### European Economic Area (EEA) and/or the United Kingdom (UK)

The controller of your personal data under our Privacy Policy is Deep State Protocol LLC, with an address of DSP, 30 N. Gould Street, Suite N, Sheridan, WY  82801.

We process your personal data only if we have a legal basis to do so, as specified in this policy.

Some of our processing of your data will involve transferring your data outside the EEA or the UK, as applicable. Some of our service providers are also based outside the EEA or UK, and their processing of your personal data will involve a transfer of data outside the EEA or UK, as applicable. This specifically includes to the United States. Where personal data is transferred to and stored in a country not determined by the European Commission as mandating by law adequate levels of protection for personal data, we take steps to provide appropriate safeguards to protect your personal data, including entering into standard contractual clauses approved by the European Commission, obliging recipients to protect your personal data.

#### California, United States

Our use of tracking technologies for advertising may be considered a "sale" under California law. To opt-out of being tracked by these third-parties go under Settings > Interface and scroll down to uncheck the "Show Adverts" box to exercise this option. Alternatively, write to us at privacy@bitchute.com. Note, however, that advertising helps us cover the cost of delivering the Service. So if you decide to exercise this option, please consider supporting the platform with a [**BitChute Membership**](https://www.bitchute.com/membership/) package. We do not knowingly sell the personal information of consumers under 16 years of age. Categories of personal information disclosed that may be considered a "sale" under California law: Device information and Other Unique Identifiers, Internet or Other Network Activity. Categories of third parties to whom personal information is disclosed that may be considered a "sale" under California law: advertisers and marketing partners, data analytics providers.

We do not share personal information with third parties for those third parties' own direct marketing purposes. Nonetheless, Californians may request information about our compliance with California's "Shine the Light" law by contacting us at [**privacy@bitchute.com**](mailto:privacy@bitchute.com) or DSP, 30 N. Gould Street, Suite N, Sheridan, WY  82801. Please provide sufficient information for us to determine if this applies to you, attest to the fact that you are a California resident, and provide your current California address to which we will send our response. Please note that we are required to respond to only one request per customer each year.

#### Nevada, United States

We currently do not sell covered information, as "sale" is defined in Nevada law, and we do not have plans to do so. If you would like to be notified if we decide in the future to sell Personal Information as defined in Nevada law, please email your name and email address to [**privacy@bitchute.com**](mailto:privacy@bitchute.com,), so that you can be contacted and instructed as to the process for opting out.

#### Virginia, Colorado, and Connecticut (United States)

In addition to the rights described above, these states' laws provide for a right to opt out of profiling and a right to appeal. We do not use Personal Information to conduct profiling. If you are unsatisfied with our actions related to one of your privacy rights above, you may appeal our decision.

How to Contact Us
-----------------

If you have any questions or concerns about our Privacy Policy or its implementation, or if you believe there are inaccuracies in your account information, please contact us at [**privacy@bitchute.com**](mailto:privacy@bitchute.com).

#### Was this article helpful?

#### Related Questions:

    Welcome to BitChute, a content sharing platform and associated services...…

    Please ensure that you use the correct email address when...…

    This Cookie Policy outlines the manner in which BitChute, a...…

Can’t find what you’re looking for?
===================================

Our customer support team is here for you.

BitChute is a peer-to-peer content sharing platform. Creators are allowed to post content they produce to the platform, so long as they comply with our [policies](https://support.bitchute.com/policy). The content posted to the platform is not reflective or representative of the views of BitChute, its staff or owners. BitChute and all associated trademarks are owned and operated by Deep State Protocol LLC. © 2017-2024 DSP LLC.
